Thank you for watching!
Best regards
Best regards.
There is no audio.
Can you hear me?
Oh, here it is.
Okay, I'll try again.
Hello again, Ugukamura Dried Television and..,
Akuna-sama. Pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
Hello. Can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
Do you hear me?
Yes, I can hear you.
Thank you very much for your patience.
Thank you for your patience. I'm sorry.
I'm sure that the new members will be coming in one after another,
So please look forward to seeing who will be joining us,
I hope you will all enjoy the distribution together with us.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much.
Today is the relay delivery of Stardust the Party.
Today is the day of Ukka.
And the first day?
No, it's not. No, it's not.
My apologies.
Yes, it is.
Rejusoara. Good evening.
I'm just, uh... I'm working.
Yes, I am.
Are you guys having fun?
Are you having fun?
Have you eaten? Dinner?
Well, it's already past 9 o'clock.
Shall we get started?
Yes, I'll be there.
First of all, Stardust the Party will be held on November 22 and 23.
I know I said two days, but on the 22nd, everyone is getting along great.
I'm going to say it a little too soon, but I'm really fond of this game.
I love this game. I'm going to tell you my real name, aren't I?
I'm going to tell you my real name, but I'm not sure if I'm going to tell you my real name, but it's an animal forest where everyone becomes an animal.
I'm also curious about the part about everyone being friends, that's great.
So, first of all, what is Star Gas the Partier?
We are a group of women who belong to Star Gas The Promotion, and we will be performing live, and we will have a lot of fun with a combination of events that you can only see on this day,
It's going to be a special party, ladies and gentlemen.
What kind of party is it? That's it.
Of course, of course, of course. First of all, I have already explained the 22nd, but on the 23rd, the second day, we will have a two-part event,
First of all, it starts at 1:00 p.m., right?
The first one starts at 1:00 p.m. Yes, that's right.
Born! StaraSong, Stapa-style MBTI diagnosis!
I love it!
Hey, Sola is already familiar with everything, MBTI.
I love MBTI, I'm so glad.
Yes, I am. I'll tell you more about it later,
And now for the last lecture, starting at 6:00 p.m,
This is Starbucks' annual singing contest!
Wow! By grade!
That means..,
We're the same!
We're here together.
It's the same here, for sure.
I see.
So, I have these three lectures,
I have a feeling that it will be a lot of fun.
I have a feeling it's going to be a lot of fun.
Yes, it is.
So, of course, you all have tickets, don't you?
Of course you have tickets.
How many people are watching now?
313 people are watching the show,
Thank you very much.
So everyone who is watching today has a ticket.
That's right.
Of course, that's what it means.
I think there are some people who haven't gotten their tickets yet,
Tickets are on sale now,
I hope you will be able to purchase tickets.
Please click the "Buy" button as you watch the video. Please do so.
It's written right here. It's right there, loud and clear.
Right at the beginning. Yes, it's this way.
Well then, let's get started.
Ah.
Ten.
We have a theme.
No.1.
A large medley with a different theme for each performance. I mentioned earlier about the M VTAs of upper-class animals and age groups, etc., and I'm looking forward to seeing many units that can only be seen there.
I am also looking forward to seeing many units that can only be seen there. Next is the second part.
The shuffle members will cover songs for this day only.
You know..,
I know that there is a word for this at the Stapler Fest, but I thought it would be fun to see the unique Stapler live performance,
But this is one of the events we can look forward to only at a live performance of STAPLA like this.
This is the one.
And, No. 3, the appearance of a new unit! A new performance of a completely original song!
Wow!
A new unit, I heard. I missed it. I mean, it's been about as long as Natsuez, hasn't it? I remember that.
Like Uta-Uma-nosuke. Or Ninny's.... There were a lot of things that happened.
But now, another new unit is going to appear in a few years. That's really nice. It's really good. I'm looking forward to it.
And number four...this is amazing. The photo-ready time is a medley of over 70 total people parading around.
A new unit.
This is amazing.
I thought it would be great to be able to take pictures of people I liked at the show and leave them on my phone for others to take pictures of, even though I didn't know many of the other groups.
That's what I mean.
That's great.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
I've seen a lot of comments on other TikToks saying that they are looking forward to seeing you at Stapa,
I can't make it to the live shows like Ukka's re-leave, but Stapa is a great place to meet people,
I'm sure there will be people who will see me there for the first time.
I am sure there will be people who will see the event for the first time.
I hope you will.
I hope you will find all kinds of people. There are many people from all walks of life.
I think the beauty of this section is that you can see many good points.
That's for sure.
I hope you can find all kinds of people and enjoy the festival. We are also looking forward to the gathering.
Oh!
Luli, please go ahead and introduce yourself. My name is Lucana Oilery. Nice to meet you.
Luri-chan is joining us. Is it this way?
Yes, I'm here.
We're up to three.
I touched three.
Are you happy?
I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy.
I'm glad.
Oh, he's calling you Ruri-chan.
I'm Ruri-chan.
Good evening, Ruri-chan.
I just ate a gummy bear.
I've just put up a link to purchase tickets in the comments section of the official Ukka website,
If you would like to purchase tickets, please click here.
I'll be waiting for you.
So far I have been explaining about units and what they do, but now I would like to talk about units.
Let's talk about the units.
This is the first unit.
Actor Selection
This is the past times...
Selection
It's a selection.
Nami Tsuji-no-Kaminami from Chotokimeki Advertising Department, Sakura Seta from Batten Shoujo-tai, Karin Tachibana from Inoue Tohoku, Moeka Suzuki from Ameflahi,
Korin Tachibana from Tohoku Inoue, Moeka Suzuki from Ameflahi,
Yuna Nakamura from Sheets Ebisu Nakaga,
I'm really looking forward to seeing what kind of unit they will become.
I'm looking forward to it.
Then, what is the order of the units that were not listed?
Yes, that's right.
Here is the first one. Next is the SNS selection.
Aki Suda from ChotokiMeki Advertising Department, Aira from Ameflasi, Mirei Hoshino from Shinsei Bijutsu Gakuin, Miu Fujisaki from One Love One Heart and Ikiari from Tohoku,
Mie Fujisaki from One Love One Heart, and Aya Datekawa from Ikinari Tohoku,
Haruna Sakamoto from Team Shirt, and oh, my gosh, Moe Serizawa! Moe Serizawa.
Moe-chan. Moe-chan.
Moe-chan has finally been selected for the unit.
Yes, first of all, Senbatsu.
Yes, I'm really looking forward to seeing what kind of unit it will be.
Good luck, Mo-chan! Good luck!
And the last one.
I wrote "A".
It's the end. Yes, it's the end.
This is the end.
And what is, you know, MVTI, the second day. Yes.
It's the second day of the MVTI diagnosis. Yes.
Okay, let's begin.
I would like to ask you, Sora-san, to help me with this. Me? Can't you read?
Then I'd like to introduce myself. Okay.
The first one is an INFP recipient. I think I'll do it this way.
Would you like me to go by Sora's side? Is that okay? Excuse me.
You know, our Sora-san is very fond of MVTI and very knowledgeable about it.
Yes, she knows a lot. I know a lot. Because, you know..,
For example, if I were an INFP, what would I be? I can answer, but I'm not so sure. I can answer, but I'm not so sure.
I'm afraid I'd have to lift the steering wheel. Okay, first of all,
The first one is Namie's first girl union, let's see..,
Nairuna, and from Shiratsuebihichugaku, Kao-chan Kobayashi, and from Ikinari Talk,
Hikaru Itsuki and Karen Tachibana. Yes, I'm sorry.
Excuse me for a moment.
I'm sorry, I don't mean to be unreasonable.
Yes, Miyu Furutani, Moeka Suzuki from Amflash, Aeon from Miss Mercy, and Himari and Aoi from Break Time Girls.
Wow!
Nine!
That's a lot!
Oh, my goodness, NFP.
Are you here?
I'm with you.
The comments have stopped.
Oh, here they come!
Some of you are with us.
Oh, and some of you have never done this before.
We've all done it this time and formed a unit, so please give it a try!
Please give it a try!
Okay, next up...
The first ENFP PR campaigner!
From our first union, Kanna Harimba!
Kanna Harimba, Ana Chihama, and Shigecha Yuhichogaku from Hatsukumiai
Sakuragi Kokoco-chan, from Chotoki Sendenbu
Hitoka Sakai-chan, from Batten Shoujo-tai
YAN-Amiyu-chan, from Ikinari-tousan-san
Datakawaya-chan, Yuna Hazuki, and Hinono-chan Sakura
And from Ukka, I, Sora Akane.
Nice, speed.
And from One Love One Heart
Ichi, Miyu Fujisaki, and Yuna Yojima from One Love One Heart.
And Miyu from Miss Mercy
And Arisa from Break Time Girls!
That's a lot of girls!
134567891011121314
14!
Wow! Oh, no!
That's a lot.
I'm looking forward to it, but it's going to be a very lively unit.
That's for sure.
Yeah.
It's going to be fun.
And next...
Next.
Oh!
Yes, INTP
INTP is Sakiko Tanaka from Namie Girls' First Union.
Eh, maybe Iwai.
Next, Yuno Kokubo from Ebiki Municipal Junior High School.
From Aten Shoujo-tai, Sakira Seta.
Oh, there are three.
Three?
That's not many.
There were so many before.
I wonder how the unit of three will turn out? I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I wonder how it will look like.
I'm sure.
Yes, and ISFJ.
Ugggghhhh.
Murahoshi Rage. That's me.
And from Miss Mercy, YUKI-chan.
This is YUKI-chan.
Two YUKI-chan.
Indeed.
Less than the previous.
I even got to take a TikTok with YUKI-chan with the two of us,
I was also able to praise her.
So we had a similar atmosphere when we met there for the first time,
I'm really looking forward to it.
What are you two like?
YUKI.
Yes, and next. INFJ.
From AmeFlash, Kojimahana-chan.
Miss Massey, Shuka-chan.
And Ebuki Mita.
What? Isn't that amazing?
Shuka-chan seems to be a big fan of Hana-chan.
She said something about that, didn't she?
That's right. So, isn't it great? She's with my guess.
It's all amazing. It's great.
It's great. It's so good.
Two.
I'm surprised to see Ibuki here. The diva.
I wonder what will happen. I wonder for sure.
I'm looking forward to it.
And next.
ESFJ.
This one is from the Nanamei Women's First Union,
Oh, Ayako Sasaki.
And Kimia Yuzu.
And from Team Shachi,
Is this the first time you've been here, Team Orca?
No, you didn't come in earlier.
No, he didn't, but he's here.
So, we have Ruki Ohguro from Team SHACHI,
And Kanami Tsujino from Chotoki-meki Propaganda Club,
and Yuriya from Break Time Girls.
Wow, I wonder what it's all about.
It's true, I don't have an image of them.
It's fresh.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Next up is ISFP,
I'll just call you by your name.
Yes, just a few names.
Yuna Nakamura, Haruka Koizumi,
Aira-chan, Miyazawa, and Yu Miyazawa from Ukka.
And Runo Iizuka,
Coconut-chan, and SARA-chan.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it.
Uka, Yuu is in the group.
What a surprise, even though the group needs a main slot.
Indeed.
Looks interesting.
And next, ISFP.
Mirei Hoshina, Haruna Sakamoto,
Ai Kiyama, Riruwa Aoi,
Mizuki Ichikawa, Ruri Aoi.
Ruri Aoi.
Ruri Aoi, right?
But you know, entertainers are really messy,
They are full of fun-loving people.
They seem to have fun, don't they?
Yeah, they seem to have fun.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, and ENFJ.
This is, let's see,
Rina, Nana Oyama,
Ayaka Yasumoto, Kazami...
Nonaka, Ema Sakurai, Hiyori Yoshikawa, Angelia, Aki Tsuda,
Rina, Nene, Hirari, Waka Yoshimori, Rina.
That's a lot, too.
Certainly a lot.
They are the protagonist type.
But they seem to be a cool group.
That's for sure.
I wonder what it will be like.
I'm looking forward to it.
Wow, there's a lot to look forward to.
There's more to come, you know.
There's so much more. Oh, no, no, no, there's so much more. And the ENTPs are RICO Mayama, RICO Ueda, and Koharu Wakano from Oka.
This is so bad. I wonder how this will turn out. I'm looking forward to this. I'm looking forward to Koharu working with these two.
I wonder what it will be like. Yes, next up. ISTJ, Rina Yuki from Oka.
Oh, one by one. You mean solo?
What do you think? I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to seeing how this one goes too.
And Nao Sakura is the only one since she tried to commercialize ENTJ.
So it's just one person. Maybe they will be together?
I wonder if that's going to happen. I'm looking forward to it.
And the ESTJs are Renu Kitami and Anri Sasaki.
Ola, two here. That's not many.
Some places have 14, some have 10, some have 2, some have 1.
Yes, that's true.
Yes, and the ISTP is Honaka Akimoto, Kina Haruno, and Shinju Yoshise.
That's three. That's not many.
Wow, but that's great.
She seems soft in terms of atmosphere.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it, too.
And last but not least, ESTP,
Riko Nakayama, and from Yuka.
It's 3DOMO.
Oh! I like Ma-chan.
Hey, we can do this with Ma-chan's guess too.
It's a co-starring.
I'm looking forward to it.
What do you think? Take a look.
I am,
Which one are you looking forward to?
I'm looking forward to Rina's solo.
For sure.
I was also looking forward to something just now. This, this, this.
I'm looking forward to this ESFJ type. I can't predict at all how it will turn out. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it. This is the group I'm looking forward to. I'm looking forward to it. Attention.
Then IS, I made a mistake, it was me. So you've introduced the MBTI diagnosis,
I'm looking forward to two days of reference with the power of the staff, but is there anything you personally are looking forward to?
I think we were able to introduce a lot of points that I am looking forward to, like the interaction.
Even I, on this first day, Friday, I was wondering, "What is this animal forest? I'm like, "What's this forest of animals? That's right! That's the point.
For example, with MVTI, I can imagine that this group is going to do something, but we don't know anything about it,
But we don't know anything about it, do we? We don't know anything about it yet. I agree.
The animal forest. Yes, that's right.
So what's going to happen? Do I become an animal?
Maybe not? What kind of animal would I be? I also pay attention to what kind of animal I will be.
For example, if I were to sing as an animal, I would be interested in how to decide who would be which animal.
I'm looking forward to it.
Is it going to be a real thing?
I want to be a daytime person.
But I'm sure it will be a miniature cat.
Yes, it's something about the way it looks.
So maybe there will be only one miniature cat,
Maybe there is.
If we go along with the FBTI, there is a possibility.
Certainly, certainly.
Yes, it is possible that there is only one miniacat.
That's right.
I wonder.
I'm not sure what you're looking forward to in your comments. I don't know.
Various things. How about you, Hina-chan? Glacier.
Maybe it's not a glacier. Maybe it's Jebula.
It's hard to say. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
The last day of the school year is the last day, or rather, the second day of the school year.
There have been many gatherings of the 04 generation, including the staff version, so I'm looking forward to seeing how it will turn out,
I'm looking forward to seeing what will happen.
With whom? For example.
Mia, Kaaya, Uni, Hinamon, and Akira Tsuda,
That's quite a lot, isn't it? Certainly.
More, more, more.
Welcome. I'm looking forward to it. Is there a second round?
I've had some great gigs with those staffs in the past,
I think I'm really looking forward to the medley. I'm really looking forward to the medley.
I'm really looking forward to it, and I'm really looking forward to the way the songs are connected,
I'm also looking forward to seeing what happens with the shuffle units, the song exchanges, and so on,
I'm really looking forward to singing other people's songs as well, so I'm really looking forward to that.
I'm also looking forward to the shuffle unit, the exchange of songs, and how it will turn out.
It's like, "There, there, there. There he is! Like, "There he is! It's over here! It's this way!
They run as fast as they can, don't they? Yes, it's fun, isn't it?
That's part of the fun, isn't it? I think everyone is looking forward to seeing it, wondering who is going to appear where.
I think people are looking forward to seeing it.
I tell Zero that it's great. It's good for 0.
It's true, I'm a zero. I'm also a zero.
Aira, Wakarin, Rine, Yuna, and Sahor.
Oh, that's right.
Who's with you? I hadn't thought about it at all. What will it be like?
It's not so common to have a line around zero, is it? It's not that easy.
That's why I'm looking forward to getting to know the kids my age. This will be a good opportunity.
Indeed. There aren't many people like Miss Mercy or the Blake Tomb Girls that I can get to know,
That's right.
This will be the first time you will be together with the members of One Love One Heart, right?
That's why I want to be friends with them.
I want to be friends with them.
It was nice to meet you when we were filming Staffer, wasn't it?
I was happy.
I was happy, wasn't I? It was great to meet you.
I'm sure the party will be very glamorous.
I hope you won't miss any of your guesses,
I hope you don't miss your guesses, find new guesses, or find a cute girl.
We are happy to be a part of it.
That's right. I hope you all have tickets, too, and comment above.
The one on the Uka channel, the one that is kind of blacked out, is on the top. Please take a look.
This is the upper part.
Press it. If you press this, you will probably be able to jump to the ticket section.
By all means.
But I'm sure that the people who are watching this distribution are also buying tickets.
372 people are watching.
372 people, right.
I'm glad for the segment. Thank you.
Yay.
Thank you.
Yeah, you know, these are the days, you know, Friday and Saturday.
Weekday.
But look, the beginning time is 6:00 p.m. Thank you very much.
So, please come and join us after work and have fun,
And if you enjoy it, there's always the next day. Yes, the next day. Happiness. Slow down already.
I'm going to fuck a lot of pretty girls. Yes, really.
Look forward to it. Two is not enough. It's not enough.
Please have them put on a lot. Lots and lots.
Work from work, indeed. That's nice.
By all means, Yokohama Bunkai. Yokohama Bunkai.
I have to take the Hankyu. That's for sure.
You may be right.
You should take the Hankyu.
What if?
If you are a little far away, I would be very happy if you could take the Hankyu,
I'll be waiting for you.
Yes, and, the goods are on sale at Stapa.
Yes, we are.
We are selling goods. What are you selling?
First of all, we are selling Stardust the Party T-shirts.
Oh!
I'm going to have to wear that.
I'm looking at it on my phone right now.
Here you go.
Stardust-o-the-Party logo on a black T-shirt.
It's pink.
It's on the upper left? It's on the upper right.
The back is very fashionable, isn't it?
Stylish!
It says "Stardus O' the Party 2024" in pink letters.
and the date is written on it.
It's a little neon, a little fashionable.
It's very cute!
And here's a Stardus O' the Party towel!
Oh, it's so cute!
Yes, this one.
Very nice.
Here it is. There's a muffler towel in the middle.
The Stardus-o-the-Party logo is right in the middle.
Around it, the logos of each group are scattered.
Isn't it really cute?
And this Stardus-o-the-Party logo is so colorful!
When you put the logos of the various groups around it, it stands out because of its colorfulness.
Yes, it's very colorful.
It's very nice.
Okay, now on to the Star Das the Party keychain!
Oh!
It's cute and stylish.
It comes in silver and gold.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It comes in two colors and is very stylish.
I think it would be very fashionable if you put it on this bag.
And...
Yes, and we have a total of 14 types of Star-Das-The-Party Consolidated Charms!
This is a key ring with the name of each group.
Each group's name is on a key chain, and you can link them together. It's nice, isn't it?
I'd love to see more of them, so I hope you'll check them out too!
And the acrylic stand!
I guess you have to have a work star for your "guess activity", right?
And the "Uka" one, too.
This is a costume of "Stapa". We made an acrylic stand with the Stapa costume, so we would be very happy if you could have it as well.
We would be very happy if you could have this one as well.
We also have can patches.
Yes!
Can patches.
Oh, it's good. Wook is cute.
Wook is cute.
It's cute. I'd be happy if you could put it on your bag or something. We are having a party.
And lastly, we have fresh photos.
Yay! I bought it for the Stardust of the Party costume.
They are so cute. And so are the outfits that each member is wearing,
All the female idol group members of Stardust are so cute, I want to have them.
So I hope you will buy them.
I see that the order sales here have already ended, folks.
So, we are only selling them on Wednesday of the same day,
So, please buy it.
If you saw this distribution and think it's cute and you want to buy it, please go early on the day of the event and buy it,
I would be very happy if you could go early on that day and buy it.
Yes, that's right.
Please do so.
It may only be for that day.
If you saw the live performance on the 22nd and thought it was really good, I think you should go early on the 23rd and get it.
That's for sure.
I really do. Very cute goods.
Someone commented that they must be expensive.
How much are they? Tell me one at a time, one more at a time. I'll tell you. First, the sizes of the T-shirts.
There are S, M, L, X, L, X, X, X, L. The size range.
And the price? The price is 3800 yen including tax.
Nice. But it says a lot. Sure.
And you can wear it all the time when you have events at Stardust. That's right. By all means.
It's a chair. And a muffler towel with the group's logo on it, easy to use. The price is 2,200 yen.
It's nice. Easy to understand. 2,200 yen. Easy to understand. It is Nyan-nyan, isn't it?
I turned 22 years old on the 19th, so I am in my nyan-nyan age. And the key chain is gold and silver. The gold and silver key chains are 1300 yen.
The price is 1300 yen.
It is very inexpensive. They are really fashionable designs, so I think they can be used as accessories for your bags or clothes.
And the 14 types of connecting charms are 800 yen.
The price is less than 1000 yen.
We hope you will get the charm of your favorite group. And 73 kinds of acrylic stands, 1500 yen.
The price is 1500 yen.
Please get your favorite Naxx, everyone.
And what else do you want?
There are 75 kinds of badges in 12 groups.
Where is it written?
Is it there?
The badges, sure.
Sorry, this is important.
The badges are random.
Sorry.
Until the feet come out.
I didn't write it down.
I'll tell you later.
And the fresh photos. Each group costs 1,000 yen.
I guess there are 5 kinds. I guess there are 5 kinds at random.
That's right.
Is that not the case?
Random 5 kinds.
Oh, that's how it is.
For one set.
Yes, per set.
About five. I'm sure it's five.
About 5 cards, that's bad.
Sometimes 6 cards.
Sometimes 3. Maybe they are signed.
Oh!
Are you sure?
The price of the badges is 500 yen.
There are a lot of badges. These are the goods here.
Please leave a fixed message above. You can see the goods on the special site,
You can also buy tickets there.
Two birds with one stone!
Wow!
That's wonderful.
Just push it over here.
I'll push it.
Se-no.
Oh, my.
Cute.
The website is cute.
Oh, and there's a video announcement on YouTube, too,
You see, even the concept of the event is listed, and the date and location are also listed.
Oh, and the ticket prices are also listed.
And?
Oh, it also has a lot of information about the fun I mentioned earlier.
And this one, too.
Yes, there is.
And you can buy tickets.
And, you know, the introduction of each group is also included.
Yes.
General tickets are available now.
Tickets are now on sale at playguide.
A little lower down, below the center of the page.
Yes, yes, a little lower.
Oh, really.
It's always at the top.
There it is.
Information
Lineup
Ticket
Goods" is next to "Tickets", isn't it?
Merchandise
Please click here.
If you press this button
You can't miss it.
Please.
Great!
By all means, everyone.
I hope the staff will look forward to seeing you.
We look forward to seeing you.
Now, I would like to come to the end.
I'm sorry I didn't make it in time for the beginning,
I hope you enjoyed it. I hope you enjoyed it as much as I did,
What do you think? What do you think? Did you get your tickets?
I'll be there! I'll be there!
I am so glad that we are able to share the excitement together through this distribution.
Thank you very much.
He said he is looking forward to it.
The last one.
Huh? No!
Really?
Yeah!
Hi!
Picota, over here.
Yes.
Hi! I'm Yukirina.
Slide in!
Slip-in!
I'm going to wait for the end.
I'm going to wait for the end. I just want to say something, something I'm looking forward to, something I want you to look at.
Um, am I alone?
I'm curious, aren't I?
I know, right?
Are you alone? Oh, that.
ISTJ.
That's right. If I was alone, I would have been there many times.
I've never seen this before.
This?
I've only started online.
Online is bad.
It's a social networking site.
Which one is this? I don't know.
Maybe the top one. That's interesting.
Hey, Nae-chan, this is the one.
Yes, you were alone.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it. I wonder what's going to happen.
I'm nervous, but I'm scared.
But Lis-chan was a back-up dancer behind me.
Did I say that?
Well, guess what?
Actually... she came in with Rina Yuki.
Who's there?
Who's there? She's not here.
One came in.
Come in, then.
Two.
Yes, sir.
Okay, so...
Yes, that's what I meant.
That was fun!
You are Yu Miyazawa, right?
I'm Yu Miyazawa.
Well then, do that.
Yes, I'm Yu Miyazawa.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, another one's here.
Why haven't they done it already?
Yoo-hoo, Mo-chan!
Yoo-hoo!
Okay, just a little lap.
Yes, sir.
Can I just say your name?
Yes, my name is
Yu Tsuruzawa.
Eee...
Yu Tsurusawa!
O-chan!
Yay!
So, you're performing in Love?
It's my first time.
It's your first time, isn't it?
Hi, I'm Yu Miyazawa.
Yoo-hoo!
Hi!
I'm Yu Miyazawa, from Kids in Love Garden.
What are you looking forward to?
What is it?
Tomorrow, right?
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
I have a lot of things to do.
You have a lot of things to do.
Heh.
I'm an animal.
An animal.
I'm curious to see what kind of animal you'll be.
It'll be fun.
Maybe a bear?
I like bears.
Sure, if it's a bear.
Ulpio.
It's Ulpio.
Urpio.
Do you have a Ma-chan?
You?
Yes, I do.
I don't know.
I mean, they're cute and all, but...
I'm more of the animal type, like rabbits.
I don't have any rabbits.
When are you talking to her? Right now.
I'm looking forward to it.
Are you looking forward to it?
Definitely animal type.
What? What kind of guy?
Definitely.
I thought so.
Definitely yes.
It's on the top.
It's not up there.
I'm looking for it.
It's obvious.
It's obvious, really.
I'm sure you've guessed that.
This is amazing.
This is it!
This is it for me.
FCGI.
Is it the same as the one you just got?
I have this one, Riko Nakayama from
Riko Nakayama.
I like her.
I'm with Riko Nakayama,
I like her a lot, so I'm happy that it's just the two of us,
I'm already looking forward to it.
That's great. I'm so happy.
We are almost at the end of our distribution,
Tomorrow is the day,
Tomorrow,
Tomorrow, this group is going to deliver.
Yes, tomorrow's delivery will be by Break Time Girls.
Yes, Break Time Girls will be broadcasting on TikTok Live.
Please wait at the distribution bar and make sure everyone is in the right place.
Yes, just like that?
Yes, sir.
I hope you are all watching, and I wonder if more and more people are watching?
Yes? How about me and Moe?
Maybe.
I was going to look for the members, but I didn't think anyone was here.
You were all over here?
That's how you distribute, right?
That's right.
I've put the URL at the top of the page, so please everyone, click on it from there,
If you haven't gotten your tickets yet, I hope you will get them for both Friday and Saturday.
Thank you very much.
Tomorrow, ah, Mr. Miyazawa's hand, right?
So, I hope you will look forward to watching Breaktime Girls tomorrow.
Then we will see you on November 22 and 23.
See you at the staff.
Bye bye.
Bye-bye.
That was Ware.
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye!
Thank you for watching.